Angel Ramirez

Aspiring UI Designer and Developer

ABOUT

Angel is a strong-believer of continuous learning and staying relevant in the ever-evolving job market. She has completed a Diploma in Web Development and Programming from Singapore Polytechnic and aspires to be a UI Designer and Developer. She has a Degree in Communication and has over 7 years of professional experience.

EXPERIENCE

Manager at Gerson Lehrman Group - Singapore June 2016 – Present (4 years)

- Special assignment Tech Liaison for Southeast Asia.
 - Spearheads internal strategic implementation of new technology solutions that improve business efficiency and expert user experience.
 - Coordinates with the APAC tech liaison head, based in Hong Kong, on technology tests and roll-outs for the region.
- Head of Philippines Councils grow the expert network by onboarding and engaging key opinion leaders, C-level executives and high-profile experts from Fortune 500 companies, large MNCs, governments, unicorns start-ups among others.
- Mentor and coach new-joiners and interns. Foster an environment where individual team members hit their KPIs.
- Started as an Associate in 2016, promoted to Senior Associate in Jan 2018 and finally to Manager in Dec 2019.

Business Development Executive at Gates PCM Integrated Services Pte. Ltd. - Singapore

March 2015 - June 2016 (1 year and 4 months)

• Achieved a "dream project" for the company - a landmark site which engages all of GPIS' services within just 2 months of employment with the company.

TV Journalist at People's Television Network. - Philippines January 2013 – January 2015 (2 years)

- Covered major beats such as:
 - Senate of the Philippines (Upper Legislative House)
 - Department of Foreign Affairs
 - Department of Finance
- Live (on-camera) coverage of various events such as natural



EDUCATION:

Diploma (Conversion) in Web and Programming

Singapore Polytechnic March 2020

Interaction Design for the Web

Lynda from LinkedIn Learning (Online Learning) March 2019

Data Analytics, Certificate

General Assembly, Singapore April 2018

Responsive Web Design

freeCodeCamp (Online learning) September 2018

Bachelor of Arts in

Communication

Graduated with Academic Honours Miriam College, Philippines March 2013

SKILLS:

